gmadeals.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy | GMA Deals

SALE ENDS Thursday, Apr 18 AT MIDNIGHT - ONLY WHILE SUPPLIES LAST

Your privacy is important to us. Our goal is to provide you with an online experience that provides you with the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. This Privacy Policy has been written to describe the conditions under which this website is being made available to you. The Privacy Policy discusses, among other things, how data obtained during your visit to this website may be collected and used. We strongly recommend that you read the Privacy Policy carefully. By using this website, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms of the Privacy Policy, you are directed to discontinue accessing or otherwise using the website or any materials obtained from it.

The process of maintaining a website is an evolving one, and GMA Deals may decide at some point in the future, without advance notice, to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your use of the website, or materials obtained from the website, indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy at the time of such use. The effective Privacy Policy will be posted on the website, and you should check upon every visit for any changes.

## Sites Covered by this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to [ www.gmadeals.com ](http://www.gmadeals.com/)

## Children’s Privacy

GMA Deals does not solicit any personal information from children, and its services are not directed to children younger than 13 years old. If you are not at least 18 years old, you are not authorized to use the website. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available from other sources on the Internet that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

## Links to Non-Operators Websites

GMA Deal’s website provides links to third-party websites for the convenience of its users. If you access those links, you will leave GMA Deal’s website. GMA Deals does not control these third-party websites and cannot represent that their policies and practices will be consistent with this Privacy Policy. For example, other websites may collect or use personal information about you in a manner different from that described in this document. Therefore, you should use other websites with caution, and you do so at your own risk. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any website before submitting personal information.

## Types of Information GMA Deals Collects

### Non-Personal Information

Non-personal information is data about usage and service operation that is not directly associated with a specific personal identity. GMA Deals may collect and analyze non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use GMA Deals’ website.

### Aggregate Information

GMA Deals may gather aggregate information, which refers to information your computer automatically provides to GMA Deals and that cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the websites you visited just before and just after GMA Deals site), the pages viewed, time spent at GMA Deals website, and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. For example, when you request a page from one of our sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns and for purposes of system administration.

### Personal Information

Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. GMA Deals uses personal information to better understand your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. You may be able to request information, subscribe to mailing lists, participate in online discussions, provide feedback or submit information into registries on GMA Deals website. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, company name or e-mail address.

## How We Use Your Information

GMA Deals may use non-personal information in the aggregate in order to improve our services and for business and administrative purposes. Non-personal information that GMA Deals collects about you may be combined by GMA Deals with other information available to GMA Deals through third parties for research and measurement purposes, including measuring the effectiveness of GMA Deals’ services and/or services offered by GMA Deals’ business partners. This information from other sources may include age, gender, demographics, geographic, or other information. GMA Deals may also use or share any such aggregated data that does not contain personal information with third parties for any purpose.

## Personal Information Sharing

GMA Deals does not sell, rent, or lease any individual’s personal information or lists of email addresses to anyone for marketing purposes. GMA Deals takes commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of this information.

GMA Deals reserves the right to disclose personal information in connection with an investigation of fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, intellectual property infringement, piracy, other unlawful activity or as otherwise required by law. In such events, GMA Deals may disclose a user’s name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company name.

## Security of Your Personal Information

GMA Deals implements physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information to which it has access. GMA Deals follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information to which it has access. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while GMA Deals strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, GMA Deals cannot guarantee its absolute security. Under no circumstances will GMA Deals be responsible or liable for any loss or damages, pecuniary or otherwise, caused by a third party’s unauthorized access to or use of your personal information. If you have any questions about security on GMA Deals’ website, you can email GMA Deals at [help@gmadeals.com](mailto:help@gmadeals.com).
